<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ABAKADA</string>
    <string name="twoCatsStory1">Once upon a time, two cats used to live in a village. They were good friends and both used to live very lovingly with each other.


One day both the cats became very hungry while playing. They saw a piece of bread at some distance.  They started fighting over that bread. One cat said,” I found it first so it is mine.” The other cat was saying the same thing.


The first cat took two pieces of bread and extended one piece towards the second cat. Seeing this, the other cat said again, "What is this, you gave me a small piece. That is wrong.


A monkey on the tree was seeing them fighting over the bread and wanted to eat that bread too. He said,’’ Why are you quarreling? I can help you because I have a scale which can divide the bread into equal amounts.”


Both cats liked the monkeys’ advice. The monkey climbed the tree and brought the scale. He put both the pieces in a pan. He deliberately divided the bread into unequal amounts and said, "Hey, this piece is big, let\'s make both equal and after saying this, he ate a little bit from the big piece and ate it.
</string>

    <string name="twoCatsStory2">

In this way, every time the scale became heavy, he broke a little bread from that side and started putting it in his mouth. Both the cats were now terrified. She still quietly waited for the monkey\'s decision as they did not want to give each other more amount of bread.


At last small pieces of bread were in pans of the scale. The monkey said, " As you have seen that I have done the hard work of dividing bread with my scale so I must get the wages of my hard work”. He ate the rest of the pieces of bread. The poor cats went on empty stomachs from there.
    </string>

    <string name="twoCatsStory3">Both the cats had realized their mistake and felt that others could take advantage of their weakness.


The Moral of the Story
This story of two cats and a monkey is indeed an amazing story with a very important lesson to learn. After reading these stories about cats, we know that we should always be careful that the third person who is watching the two friends fighting is not helping. On the contrary, he is taking advantage of the fight and he is using the two friends for his own benefit. This story teaches us that “when two people fight, it’s always the third person who gets the benefit”.
    </string>


    <string name="theLionStory1">
        Years and years ago, once there was a lion sleeping in the forest under a big tree. A mouse, who lived in the forest too, started playing while moving up and down the lion’s body. She also accidentally ran across the lion’s nose once.
    </string>

    <string name="theLionStory2">
        This soon awakened the lion, and he held the little mouse in his paws. The mouse began to tremble as he knew that the lion was angry and could kill him right there. "Pardon, O King!" pleaded the little mouse. "Forgive me this time. I shall never repeat it, and I shall never forget your kindness. Who knows, I may be able to give you a good turn one of these days!”


The lion was somehow in a good mood. Hence, he set the mouse free from his paws. Yet he could not be more amused by the idea of how a tiny mouse could ever help the king of the jungle.


After a few days, the mouse suddenly heard the roar of the lion. When she went to look at what’s the matter, she found out that the lion was captured and trapped in a net by his prey. Seeing the lion in such a condition, she immediately started gnawing the ropes of the net until it freed the lion.
    </string>

    <string name="theLionStory3">
        The lion thanked the little mouse. But the mouse was happy that she could finally repay her debt for sparing her life once. Since then the lion and mouse became good friends, and they lived happily ever after.
    </string>


</resources>